我已经无人可挡了
I was unstoppable.
我是说 我... 我状态太好了
I mean, I was... I was on fire.
就好像我的身心都融为了一体
It was like my mind and my body were totally connected,
就像... 像运动员找到感觉的时候一样
like... like athletes must feel when they're in the zone.
我再说一遍 不就是迷你高尔夫吗
Again, it was miniature golf.
承认吧 你也玩得挺嗨
Admit it, you're a little turned on.
你不能这么骄傲啊
You can't be this proud.
为什么?
Why not?
因为我打败你了
Because I beat you.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
哦 不错 你回来了
Oh, good. You're back.
我们有个激动人心的消息
We have some exciting news.
好吧
Okay.
你们也知道 Amy和我已经在一起很长时间了
As you know, Amy and I have been together a long time,
很多我曾经觉得不可能的事
and a lot of things
现在变得可能了
I never thought possible now seem possible.
然后呢...
Okay...
我们对我们的关系做了非常仔细的评估
After a careful evaluation of our relationship,
并决定 是时候向前迈一步了
we decided that the time was right to take a step forward.
好吧
Okay.
你想说吗?
Do you want to say it?
我们一起说吧
Let's say it together.
我们要养一只乌龟!
We're getting a turtle!
我就知道我们不能急着庆祝
This is why I've been saying we should keep champagne on ice.
这是讽刺吗?
Sarcasm?
- 是的  - 好的
- Yes.  - Okay.
那个有点难懂 因为她谈到酒的时候
That was tricky, 'cause when it comes to alcohol,
一般来说都可认真了
she generally means business.
呃 我们... 我们为你们感到高兴
Well, we're... we're very happy for you.
是的
Yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
一起养一只宠物是我们关系的一大步
Acquiring a joint pet is a big step for us.
是啊 真的
No. It's true.
这意味着我们之间多出来的关心
It means that we care so much about each other,
都够分给一只8盎司的爬行动物了
there's enough left over for an eight-ounce reptile.
为什么要养乌龟?
Why a turtle?
在权衡利弊之后 我们觉得一只乌龟
After much deliberation, we've determined that a turtle
是最理想的宠物
is the ideal pet.
他们不会掉毛 不会发出噪音...
They don't shed fur, they don't make noise...
在万圣节的时候 我们可以把他打扮成一块石头
For Halloween, we can dress him as a cobblestone.
是啊
Yeah.
而且如果他发狂的话 我也能跑得过他
And if he ever goes berserk, I know I can outrun him.
真巧 我选你做我的室友也是因为这个原因
Coincidentally, that's also why I chose you as a roommate.
那恭喜你们
Well, congratulations.
谁能想到 你们两个是我们这群人当中
Who would've thought you two would be the first
- 第一个成家的?  - 嗯
- in our group to start a family?  - Mm-hmm.
我刚就这么说了!
That's what I said!
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季17集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 不会算数的凤梨酥
翻译: 黄字君 凤梨酥 奥利奥
校对: UU养了只狐狸叫查理
呃 你室友今晚去哪了?
So, where's your roommate tonight?
呃 我觉得你每次来她都在
Well, I thought it was a little unfair
然后你一直都没有机会
that she's always here, and you never
在我家留宿 所以... 我把她杀了
get a chance to stay over, so... I killed her.
但是你还记得我们之间的约定吗?
But remember our agreement?
你可以拿杀人来开玩笑
You can joke about murdering people,
但是你一定得说"开玩笑的"
but you have to say, “Just kidding.”
更重要的是要记住
And the more important thing to remember is
我永远不会伤害你的
that I'd never hurt you.
好烦
Oh, crap.
我得赶到医院去检查一个病人
I have to run over to the hospital and check on a patient.
- 没事的 我等等再来吧  - 别啊
- That's okay. I can come back later.  - No.
不用的 别犯傻
No, don't be silly.
我不会离开很久的 你留在这里吧
I won't be gone long. Just stay here.
好的 没事
Okay, cool.
对了 你确定我一个人在这里的时候
Oh, and you're sure your roommate's
你的室友不会回来吗?
not gonna come back while I'm here alone, right?
因为那样的话就会比较尴尬了
'Cause that'll be awkward.
哦 别担心 她在棕榈泉
Oh, don't worry. She's in Palm Springs.
哦 那就好
Oh, good.
其实是她的躯干在哪里
Well, her torso is.
开玩笑的啦
Just kidding.
我把她放在木材削片机里了
I put her in a wood chipper.
哦天啊 哦天啊
Oh, dear Lord. Oh, dear Lord.
没事的
It's okay.
你成功了 我们没事了
You made it. We're fine.
那里有好多小狗啊
That was a lot of puppies.
忘了它们吧 然后...
Let's forget about them, and...
给我们自己挑一只漂亮的乌龟
pick ourselves out a nice turtle.
是啊 哦 这只趴在木头上的怎么样?
Yeah. Oh, how about this one up on the log?
哦 这个我不太喜欢
Oh, I don't know.
他看上去有点混蛋
He kind of looks like a jerk.
那这只怎么样?
How about this one?
呃 他都没怎么动 他看上去半死不活的
Well, he's barely moving. He looks half dead.
我知道 我也喜欢他
I know. I like him, too.
你好啊 小家伙
Hi, little guy.
你想和我们回家吗?
How'd you like to come home with us?
你会和我住在一起 因为我们俩是分开住的
You'll be living with me because we don't live in the same house.
但那不是你的错
But that's not your fault.
我们和你一样 (恋情进展)速度非常缓慢
Like you, we're taking it ridiculously slow.
当他去漫展 或者出差的时候 你就和我待在一起
You'll stay with me when he's at Comic-Con or away for work.
或者如果他们批准了你爹地上火星生活的申请
Or if they accept Daddy's application to live on Mars.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
哦 有一个公司
Oh, there's this company
想要在火星上建立一个殖民地
that's attempting to establish a colony on Mars,
我申请成为去那边的第一批人
and I applied to be among the first to go.
我们给他取个什么名字好呢?
What should we name him?
你知道吗 我进来的时候还想用"Seth" 但...
You know, I came in thinking “Seth,” but...
他有点像是意大利来的
he kind of looks Italian.
你去申请加入一个
You applied for a mission
去另一个行星殖民的任务
to be a colonist on another planet,
竟然不告诉我?
and couldn't be bothered to tell me?
你会同意吗?
Would you have approved?
当然不会
Of course not.
那既然你是这个反应
Well, based on your reaction,
看来我做得对
it looks like I made the right choice.
对不对呀 Giuseppe?
Isn't that right, Giuseppe?
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
听着 我... 我要坦白一件事
Listen, I... I have a little confession to make.
噢 你是第一次吗?
Aw, is this your first time?
不是啊 我给你搞了个情人节礼物
No, I got you something for Valentine's Day,
但我不好意思给你
and I was too embarrassed to give it to you.
啊 为什么?
Well, why?
呃 因为我是在情趣用品店买的
Well, 'cause I got it at the dirty store.
你去情趣店没叫上我?!
You went to the dirty store without me?!
我戴着墨镜和帽子 还把车子停在了两条街之外
In sunglasses and a hat after I parked two blocks away.
- 啊 快去拿! 拿来给我!  - 确定?
- Well, get it! Get it for me!  - Yeah?
- 对啊  - 好吧 呃 我希望它好玩
- Yeah.  - Okay, uh, well, I hope it's fun.
我是说 它... 它上面有颜料 而且... 而且
I mean, it... it comes with paints, and... and
它很有创意 而且很有艺术感
it's kind of creative and artistic.
等等 你是去了情趣用品店还是去了手工艺品店啊?
Okay, did you go to the dirty store or Michaels?
不是啊
No, no.
我们在在自己身上涂上颜料
We cover ourselves in body paint,
然... 然后我们到这块画布上 你懂的
and then... then we get on this big canvas and do our thing.
哇 这对于一个最近才同意脱袜子的男人来说
Whoa, that's kind of a big step for a guy
可是向前迈了一大步啊
who only recently agreed to take his socks off.
你在嘲笑我呢 算了吧
You're making fun of me. Forget it.
- 别啊! 别啊 来吧 我想干  - 真的?
- No! No, come on, I want to do it.  - Really?
是啊 让你我
Yeah, let's you, me,
还有你那白花花的小脚一起来做艺术吧
and your very, very pale feet make some art.
嘿 你再去那个商店的时候 我也要一起去
Hey, when you got back to this store, I want to go with you.
好啊 不过得开好长时间的车呢... 这个我是去圣地亚哥买的
Okay, but it's a drive... the one I went to is in San Diego.
税务怎么样?
How are the taxes going?
还行吧
Okay.
但你有好多乐高的收据
But you got a lot of receipts for the Lego store in here.
那些是生意花销
Those are business expenses.
你可以把它划掉的
You can write those off.
一个两百刀的R2-D2机器人是工作支出?
A $200 R2-D2 is a business expense?
哦 Bernie
Oh, Bernie,
要是有人来查我们的帐
you're gonna have to sound a lot more confident
求你别用这种语气
when we get audited.
喂 怎么了?
Hey, what's up?
额 Emily回医院去了
Eh, Emily ran back to the hospital,
所以我现在一个人在她家待着呢
so I'm just hanging out at her place.
你干什么呢?
What are you, uh, what are you doing?
Bernie在弄报税的事 我在打游戏
Just playing video games while Bernie does the taxes.
你是小孩吗?
What are you, a little kid?
她是不是还会帮你把食物切成小块?
Is she gonna cut your dinner into little pieces, too?
不用啊... 我自己会吃果冻糖的
She doesn't have to... I filled up on jelly beans.
好吧 你在玩...
So, uh, what game are you...
啊
Oh.
天啊
Crap.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我关不上Emily的床头柜了
I can't get Emily's nightstand to close.
那怎么了?
So?
她会知道我偷偷翻她的床头柜的
She's gonna know I was looking in it.
你为什么要翻啊?
Why were you looking in it?
这是个好问题
Well, there's a question
我得在她回来之前想个靠谱的答案
I better have a good answer to before she gets back.
淡定点 没事的
Okay, calm down.
可能是后面有东西卡住了
There's probably something jammed behind it.
把抽屉拉出来看看里面有什么就好
Just, uh, pull it out and see what's there.
等一下
Hang on.
哦...不是吧
Oh... no. Oh, no.
天啊 怎么会这样!
Oh, God, no!
那个 你那好像不太好... 我先挂了啊
You know what, you sound busy... I'm gonna let you go.
天啊 整个抽屉前面的挡板都掉了
Dude, the whole front came off.
现在她肯定会知道我在偷窥她的私人物品了
Now she's gonna know I was snooping.
怎么了?
What's happening?
Raj正在偷看Emily的抽屉 还把抽屉弄坏了
Raj was snooping through Emily's drawers and broke one.
天啊
Aw.
他们分手之后我会想念她的
I'm gonna miss her.
你觉得怎么样?
So what do you think?
我还以为画面能再...至少丰富一点吧
I thought it'd be a little more... just more.
真不敢相信我们都快喘不上气了
I'm not even sure why we were out of breath.
额 咱俩... 动了么?
Uh, I mean, d...did we move at all?
可能我们上下动得比较多
Maybe along the z-axis,
平面方向看起来真是悲伤
but x and y are looking pretty sad.
不行 不行
Okay, come on.
我们又不是无聊的老头老太太
We are not old boring people.
咱们肯定能玩出更多花样的
We can do better than this.
额 这... 有道理
Uh, Th...that's true.
咱们昨晚几点睡的?
How late did we stay up last night?
凌晨一点左右吧
Almost 1:00 a.m.
我了个去 一点左右啊
Damn straight, almost 1:00 a.m.
咱们也没看电视
And we weren't even watching TV.
咱们看Netflix来着 年轻人都看这个
We were watching Netflix, like the kids do.
(Netflix是美国在线影片租赁提供商)
是啊 咱们看的是动画片么?
Yeah, is it a comedy?
还是剧情片来着?
Is it a drama?
不记得了
Nobody knows.
来来来
Now, come on.
咱们再来一次
We are gonna do this. Yeah.
你准备颜料 我休息个三四十分钟
You get the paint, I'll rest for 30-40 minutes,
然后咱们再来一回合!
and then we do this!
真不敢相信 你差点让我
I can't believe you almost had me bring
带一只野兽回家
a wild animal into my home.
没人会去戳乌龟的脸
No one told you to poke the turtle's face.
我在和它玩"抓鼻子"的游戏
I was playing "Got Your Nose"
这样才能跟孩子们亲近
That's how you get children to like you.
我真没想到 你一有机会
I'm surprised you even care if he likes you,
就打算离开地球了 居然还在乎
since you're planning on leaving the planet
它喜不喜欢你
the first chance you get.
啊 又说起来这个了
Ugh, this again.
Amy 我今天已经受过一次伤了
Amy, I've already had one new hole torn in my body today.
别让我再受伤了
I don't need another one.
Sheldon 我知道
Sheldon, I know the odds
你能去火星的几率很小很小
of you even going to Mars are incredibly small,
但是知道你自愿参加 可能会让你永远离开我的事情
but it still hurts that you would volunteer for something
我还是很伤心
that would take you away from me forever.
你是说 你不会为了成为
So you're saying you wouldn't leave me
第一个移民到其他星球的人类
for the chance to be one of the first humans
而离开我?
to colonize another planet?
我至少会在申请之前
I would at least mention it
告诉你一声
before filling out the application.
哈 Leonard Wolowitz Koothrappali
Huh, that's exactly what Leonard, Wolowitz, Koothrappali,
Bernadette和Penny都是这么说的
Bernadette and Penny said.
再说了 谁又能保证你们能
And who says you could even survive
在这样的星际旅行中活下来?
an interplanetary mission, anyway?
你连被乌龟咬了一口你都差点死过去
You could barely survive a tiny turtle bite.
首先 这样的伤...
First of all, this...
只会使我变得更加坚强
has only made me stronger.
不过 到现在为止
But beyond that, all I did
我也不过就是填了个申请表而已
was fill out an application.
算了
You know what?
Sheldon 去火星吧
Go to Mars, Sheldon.
有什么办法能让你开心吗?
Is there anything I can do to cheer you up?
没有 别想了
No. Forget it.
我用鼻子给你吹星际迷航的主题曲怎么样?
What if I play the Star Trek theme on my nose?
千万别
Please don't.
好吧 看来你真的生气了
Yep, you're mad.
让我看看现在是什么状况
Okay, let me see the damage.
稍等一下
Hang on.
我觉得你好象把螺钉弄坏了
Well, I think you broke the dowels.
粘起来的话
You're not gonna have time to glue it
肯定是...来不及了 你得把它钉好
back on... you'll have to nail it.
用什么啊?
With what?
她有没有枕头或者玻璃杯?
Does she have any pillows or wine glasses?
有啊
She does.
太好了
Great.
这些都没用啊白痴 要用锤子!
Neither of those. Try a hammer!
你喜欢这种感觉?
Did that feel good?
好像你最牛似的?
You feel like a big man now?
我本来想给你做玫瑰茄茶的
I was going to make you Red Zinger,
不过火星也是红色的
but since Mars is the red planet,
我就改做薄荷茶了
I went with peppermint.
你为什么想去火星啊?
Why do you even want to do this?
说到这个...
Actually...
作为申请的一部分
as part of the application,
他们让我做一个视频
I was required to make a short video
来回答这个问题
answering that very question.
你要看看吗?
You want to see it?
你就不能直接告诉我吗?
Can't you just tell me?
可是我做了视频呀
But I made a video.
我是Sheldon Copper博士
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
而我想告诉你们 我为什么应该...
and I'd like to tell you why I should be chosen to...
去火星!
go to Mars!
我超级聪明
I'm exceedingly smart.
十四岁大学毕业
I graduated college at 14.
我哥哥感染性病的时候
While my brother was getting an STD
我就已经是博士了
I was getting a PhD.
青霉素可治不好高智商呦
Penicillin can't take this away.
如果居住空间狭小的话 卫生就会显得非常重要
Being in close quarters, cleanliness is important
而...我的个人卫生无可挑剔
and... my hygiene is impeccable.
事实上 动物们都不喜欢我
In fact, animals don't trust me
因为我闻起来毫无味道
because I smell like nothing.
真的...
Yeah...
毫无异味
Literally nothing.
在七个月的太空飞行期间
During the seven-month space flight,
我可以用我独特的幽默感鼓舞大家
I can keep up morale with my wacky sense of humor.
嘿 Leonard...
Hey, Leonard...
盒子里还有花生饼干吗?
is there any peanut brittle left in that can?
这个莫名其妙的盒子?
You mean this weirdly suspicious one?
是啊 打开看看吧
Yes. Open it and check.
又是什么意思
I don't get it.
真的有花生饼干在...
There's actually peanut brittle in...
快滚去火星吧
Please go to Mars.
不过言归正传:
But on a more serious note:
我想去火星最重要的原因是
The most important reason I want
我相信 作为一名科学家
to go to Mars is that I believe, as a scientist,
我的使命就是不断推动
it's my duty to push the boundaries
人类知识的发展
of human knowledge forward.
我深知在火星上生存极为困难
Now, I know that life on Mars will be difficult.
但生活在地球上也非小菜一碟
But life here on Earth is no picnic.
还有 小菜也非小菜一碟
Also, picnics are no picnic.
我们去哪里吃午饭?
Where should we go for lunch?
哦 我知道了 去地底下
Oh, I know, the ground.
总而言之
In conclusion,
感谢您考虑让我
thank you for considering me
参与此次"一生之旅"
for this journey of a lifetime.
登上火星!
To Mars!
后来 Leonard擤了下鼻涕
Afterwards, Leonard blew his nose,
结果派喷了出来
and pie came out.
就是那儿 就是那儿
Right there, right there,
天哪 就是这样!
Oh, God, that's it!
你眼睛里怎么进颜料的?
How did you get paint in your eye?
都怪你不肯让我戴防护眼镜!
Because you wouldn't let me wear safety goggles!
这活儿看着糟透了
This looks terrible.
她... 她绝对会发现的
She... she's gonna know.
没事的
It's fine.
你只需要再多两个钉子
You just need two more nails.
好吧 钉在哪里?
Okay, where should I put them?
Emily的眼睛里
In Emily's eyes.
你只会添乱子
You're not helping.
或许这是你偷窥隐私的报应
Well, maybe this is what you get for snooping.
要知道 光... 光是搞定这个就够我烦的了
You know, it... it's bad enough that I have to deal with this...
Raj? 我回来啦
Raj? I'm back.
哦 不好
Oh, no.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
医院里怎么样?
How was the hospital?
还好啊
Fine.
你在那里做什么呢?
What were you doing in there?
呃... 这... 这个
Uh... w... well...
好吧 听着 我... 我不想骗你
Okay, look, I... I don't want to lie to you.
我... 我有点好奇 就四处乱翻...
I... I got curious, I was looking around...
然后弄坏了你床头柜的抽屉
and I broke the drawer on your night stand.
你翻了我的床头柜?
You were looking in my night stand?
是的
Yeah.
所以第一次留你在我家
So, the first time I leave you alone,
你就偷窥我隐私?
you snoop on me?
你从来没翻查过我的房间吗?
You've never snooped around my apartment?
- 没有!  - 拜托啦 好好想想
- No!  - Come on, think back.
要是真有 就帮我大忙了!
It would really help if you had!
真不敢相信你居然不信任我!
I can't believe you don't trust me!
她听起来真的很生气
She sounds really mad.
我们应该挂电话
We should hang up.
是啊 是该挂
Yeah, we should.
但我们不打算这么做 对吧?
But we're not going to, are we?
想都别想
Not a chance.
那我们不管"偷窥有罪"啦?
What happened to "snooping is wrong"?
Howard 你反正要因偷税坐牢的
Howard, you're going to jail for tax fraud.
谁管这个?
Who cares?
我们做到了
Well, we did it.
我们真做到了
We sure did.
我刚才真是干劲十足!
I mean, I was on fire!
很... 很在状态 就像个运动员
I... I was in the zone, like an athlete.
亲爱的 我在这方面也比你强
Sweetie, I beat you at this, too.
那我们把它挂在哪呢?
So, where do we want to hang it?
什么? 你在开玩笑吗?
What? Are you kidding?
我们才不把它挂起来!
We're not hanging it!
不过它是我们爱的描绘啊
But it's an expression of our love.
还有我们的屁股! 才不挂它!
And our butts! Not hanging it!
那要是丢了它 有点丢人吧
Seems a shame to throw it away.
是啊
Yeah.
我们可以把它送给Sheldon
We could give it to Sheldon,
威廉·夏特纳: 电影"星际旅行"中饰演舰长詹姆斯
说是威廉·夏特纳画的
and tell him William Shatner painted it.
天哪 我爱你 我爱死你了
God, I love you. I love you so much.
我觉得我该回家了
I think I'm gonna go home.
为什么?
Why?
我真没弄明白现在的状况
I really don't understand what's happening here.
要知道 Sheldon 换做平时
You know, Sheldon, at any other time,
得知你计划去火星生活
learning that you had plans to go live on Mars
也没什么大不了的
would be a slow news day.
但就在几个小时前
But a couple of hours ago,
我们准备养只乌龟
we were getting a turtle.
听起来可能很傻
And silly as it sounds,
可我还以为那别有意义呢
I thought that meant something.
喂Amy!
Amy!
哦 为什么没给她泡杯宁神茶呢?
Oh, why didn't I give her Sleepy Time tea?
Amy 等等!
Amy, wait!
养只乌龟对我也意义非凡
Getting a turtle meant a great deal to me, too.
当然
Sure.
除非你碰上其他更好的事
Unless something better comes along.
你想要我撤回申请吗?
Do you want me to withdraw my application?
我想要的是让我们
What I want is for us
一起为未来做打算
to be planning our future together.
那在那个未来里
And in that future,
我们生活在同一个星球吗?
are we on the same planet?
那是因为我遇到过
Yeah, because I've seen people
有人谈得成异地恋的
make the long-distance thing work.
- 我们生活在一个星球上!  - 好的!
- We're on the same planet!  - Okay!
那个星球一定要是地球吗?
Does that planet have to be Earth?
你是在邀请我陪你一起去火星吗?
Are you asking me to go to Mars with you?
是的
I am.
如果我要去一个荒凉的
Yeah, if I'm going to a barren,
没有生命的环境
lifeless environment,
在那存活的几率几乎是零
where the chances of survival are slim to none,
我希望你也在那陪我
I want you there with me.
我们回房间
Why don't we go back to the apartment,
把你的申请填好吧?
and fill out your application?
好的
Okay.
我在想 成为住在新星球的
I suppose being the first people
第一对情侣会是无比的激动人心
on a new planet would be incredibly exciting.
哦 我知道
Oh, I know.
我们可以是第一对在火星上插上国旗的情侣
We could be the first to plant a flag on Mars.
我们可以是第一对在火星上观看"火星入侵"的情侣
We could be the first to watch Mars Attacks! on Mars.
我们可以是第一对说"天哪
We could be the first to say “Good Lord,
你在说什么火星话"的情侣
what on Mars are you talking about"
你要知道
You know,
我们也可以是第一对
we could also be the first people
在火星上繁衍后代的情侣
to procreate on Mars.
你的宇航服裤就没法好好穿着 是吧?
You just can't keep it in your space pants, can you?
仔细想想
Think about it.
我们要是在那成了家
If we had a family there,
我们的孩子就会是火星人
our kids would be Martians.
他们会的 对吧?
They would, wouldn't they?
我们可以给他们起帅气的火星名
We could give them cool Martian names.
我们可以教他们火星历史
And we could teach them about Martian history.
比如 是谁插的那些国旗?
Like, who planted those flags?
还有那份"火星入侵"的碟子
And, uh, where did that copy
是哪里来的?
of Mars Attacks! come from?
我想我们要以夫妻的身份
I guess we'll have to make
一起重新录段视频
a new video together, as a couple.
好主意
Good idea.
而且考虑到你今天这么辛苦
And since you've had such a rough day,
就让你来把派砸Leonard脸上好了
I'm gonna let you throw the pie in Leonard's face.
谢谢你原谅了我
Thank you for forgiving me.
没事的
It's okay.
某时某刻 我们注定会吵一架的
At some point, we were bound to have our first fight.
上次你说我的苹果派是硬皮的"生面团"时
Well, it almost happened when you called
我就差点想吵架了
my apple pie crust "doughy"
事实是你没有错
The truth is you were right.
我只是在生自己的气
And I was just angry at myself.
我能问你件事吗?
Can I ask you one thing?
当然 什么事?
Of course. What?
你翻了我的衣柜吗?
Did you look in my closet?
没有 只是抽屉而已
No. Just the drawer.
你保证你没翻过衣柜?
You promise you didn't look in the closet?
我保证
I promise.
怎么了 里面有什么吗?
Why, what's in there?
没什么
Don't worry about it.
晚安
Good night.
结尾有特别内容
致 伦纳德·尼莫伊 (星际迷航中饰演大副Spock)
你给我们的剧和生活带来的影响是永恒的